[{"answer": "Well, it's very clear that the crisis that erupted in the United States, the financial crisis, three years ago, specifically in the summer of 2007 -- that's where the whole thing began -- showed that capitalism was -- went out of control.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What do you think has gone wrong with the American business model, and how can they fix it?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, clearly Apple is a role model of the American innovation whereby it produced all these products -- iPod, iPhone, iPad -- that are really now dominating all the technology arena in the world.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "I mean do you think it's time they went back to designing, creating, and building things that they can sell to the world exactly as Apple is doing so successfully?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, clearly, as we have read recently in the board of directors over there, has begun looking and talking about succession.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Are you concerned at all about the succession plans at Apple given the ongoing situation involving Steve Jobs' health?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, you know, News Corp is the only real media global -- that has a global presence that's involved in TV production, in movies, in publishing, in newspapers, digital media, et cetera.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Are you happy with the way things are?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I went public by supporting Mr. Rupert and Mr. James after the hearings because I know them very well.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Does James and Rupert both retain your full support?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, it's very clear that the Arab population is rising because they'd like to have a say in the running of their affairs, running of their government, and this is very legitimate.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What did you make of it from Saudi Arabia?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Thanks god Saudi Arabia is very stable.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "How would you say the mood is in Saudi Arabia about what's going on?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "I don't agree I'm a lonely voice because all what I tell you right now, my friend Piers, I say that in public in Saudi Arabia, and the majority of Saudis are with me.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Are you pushing your colleagues there in government to be as progressive as you've just been sounding?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm a member of the royal family but not a member of the government.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "In terms of Saudi's role with terrorism and with al Qaeda, do you think that Saudi should be harder and tougher against Islamic fundamentalism than it has been?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, I think that Colonel Gadhafi's days are really numbered.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Do you think it's time that he just stood down now?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, royalty in the UK is very popular, not only in United Kingdom but all the world, and I think that what's happening between the new couple is really a replica, a duplication what happened between Prince Charles and the late Princess Diana.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Now what do you make of them as a couple and the impact they're now having globally?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's clear that we don't know.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Where are we as things stand?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "It depends on whether you -- how you raise revenue, I think.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Would you both concur that that is where we are now in terms of public opinion?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "What I think we have to do is we have to reform our tax code in a way that promotes economic growth and not just add tax increases on it to meet a certain number in the budget to say we got a deal.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "I mean are we now in a position with the American economy where thinking the unthinkable has to be the way to go?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "The fact you've come together and you've put a proposal together which seems to have been the catalyst for what may well be a deal on this, is this a way of both parties saying, OK, things did get a bit out of hand?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Where are we going here?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "This one's so new, I can't weigh in on it yet.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Frank, come on, which of all these myriad of roles that you've had have you most enjoyed, do you think?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "The women wouldn't have done so much for me.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What's not to love, huh?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "RUNI: You know, I do.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Do you like that kind of freedom, where you can literally choose anything that rocks your boat?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "You know, I get -- where the world has changed so much, I get amazingly lovely e-mails from readers when I write about that topic.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "How is that kind of column going down generally?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "America's status as the sole super power is in real peril, isn't it?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Well part of the answer is an end to the kind of polarized politics and bickering that we have.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "We've all been reckless.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "How much do you blame the American public for being reckless with their own spending?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I think he's trying very hard to lead right now.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Is President Obama lacking leadership, do you think?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "You know, we're the two individuals who can't answer that because we haven't read or watched Harry Potter.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Why is the world so obsessed with Harry Potter, if you and I, two reasonably intelligent individuals, have this completely passing us by?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "You know, I tuned into it kind of late.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What was your take on it?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "To me, when I watch her, her degree of hyperbole and hysteria doesn't feel to me like passion on behalf of victims solely.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Is that what you feel?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "No, no, it was a fantastic job.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Do you regret ever getting involved in restaurant critique?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "You know, I get asked that --", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What was the single best meal you've ever had in a restaurant?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Have you eaten there?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "I would love to say that the five and half years as restaurant critic put me off food and now I have to force myself to eat.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Or did it get quenched by al this gorging over the years?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Oddly, it has hurt me.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Has it helped you giving up the restaurant critiques?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Well, no, I still live here in New York and I spend most of my time here.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Are you mad?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "No, it's a whole -- I was in Washington last -- I lived there from 1998 to 2002, before I went to Rome.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Do you feel like it's this terrible thing, like an addiction?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I think any smart better right now would have to say it's going to be Mitt Romney.", "docId": "110721pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Do you see a potential winner in a race against President Obama?", "qSentId": 456}]